let DT_trials = [
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_17', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_24', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAA_TAA_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAA_TAA_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_8', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_19', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_27', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_28', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_29', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DAH_TAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DAH_TAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_21', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DIH_TIH_3_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DIH_TIH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_8', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_17', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_24', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_28', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>T</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>D</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'DT_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'DT_test', audio: 'DUH_TUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'D', voiceless_sel: 'T', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_DT/DUH_TUH_3_30.wav' }}]